Guide to the Department of History, Yale University, Records
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
- Personnel records of faculty, 1958-1997; Accession 2003-A-065
  - Professors
    - Assoc. Professors, Lecturers, Visiting Professors, Research Fellows, etc.
    - Calvo-Ely (Box 2, Folder 23)
    - Misc. D's (Box 2, Folder 59)
    - Emerson-Hackney (Box 3, Folder 80)
    - H's (Box 3, Folder 141)
    - Levi -Moore (Box 5, Folder 174)
    - Abitbol -Butler (Box 6, Folder 225)
    - Miscellaneous A's (Box 6, Folder 239)
    - Karpovich-Lemisch (Box 7, Folder 281)
    - K's (Box 7, Folder 311)
    - Mote-Ripley (Box 8, Folder 321)
    - P's (Box 8, Folder 357)
    - Professors
  - Assoc. professors, lecturers, visiting professors, research fellows, etc.
    - Graziosi Conference (Box 14, Folder 512)
    - Middlekauff Lecture (Box 14, Folder 539)
- Course evaluations, 1998-2000; Accession 2004-A-022
  Restricted until Jan 1, 2076
- Dissertation readers' reports, 1963-1993; Accession 2003-A-139
  Restricted until Jan 1, 2069
  - 1963-1964 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - 1964-1965 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Fall 1965 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - 1966 Jun (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - 1966 Sep (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - 1967 Jun (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - 1967 Sep (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - 1968 Jun (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - 1968 Sep (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - 1969 Jun (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - 1969 Dec (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - 1970 Feb (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - 1970 Jun (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - 1970 Dec (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - 1971 Feb (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - 1971 Jun (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - 1971 Sep (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - 1972 Feb (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - 1972 Sep (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - 1973 Mar (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - 1973 Jun (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - 1973 Dec (Box 1, Folder 22)
  - 1974 May (Box 1, Folder 23)
  - 1974 Dec (Box 1, Folder 24)
  - Spring 1975 (Box 1, Folder 25)
  - 1975 Dec (Box 1, Folder 26)
  - Spring 1976 (Box 1, Folder 27)
  - 1976 Dec (Box 1, Folder 28)
  - Spring 1977 (Box 1, Folder 29)
  - 1977 Dec (Box 1, Folder 30)
  - 1978 May (Box 1, Folder 31)
  - 1978 Dec (Box 1, Folder 32)
  - Spring 1979 (Box 1, Folder 33)
  - 1980 May (Box 2, Folder 34)
  - 1980 Dec (Box 2, Folder 35)
  - 1981 May (Box 2, Folder 36)
  - Fall 1981 (Box 2, Folder 37)
  - 1982 May (Box 2, Folder 38)
  - 1982 Dec (Box 2, Folder 39)
  - 1983 May (Box 2, Folder 40)
  - 1983 Dec (Box 2, Folder 41)
  - 1984 May (Box 2, Folder 42)
  - 1984 Dec (Box 2, Folder 43)
  - Spring 1985 (Box 2, Folder 44)
  - Fall 1985 (Box 2, Folder 45)
  - Spring 1986 (Box 2, Folder 46)
  - 1986 Dec (Box 2, Folder 47)
  - 1987 May (Box 2, Folder 48)
  - 1987 Dec (Box 2, Folder 49)
  - 1988 May (Box 2, Folder 50)
  - Fall 1988 (Box 2, Folder 51)
  - 1989 May (Box 2, Folder 52)
  - Fall 1989 (Box 2, Folder 53)
  - Spring 1990 (Box 2, Folder 54)
  - Fall 1990 (Box 2, Folder 55)
  - 1991 May (Box 2, Folder 56)
  - Fall 1991 (Box 2, Folder 57)
  - Fall 1992 (Box 2, Folder 58)
  - 1993 Dec (Box 2, Folder 59)
- Records, 1923-2003; Accession 2013-A-040
  Restricted until January 1, 2078.
  - Annual Reports
    - 1957-1958 (Box 1, Folder 1)
    - 1962-1963 (Box 1, Folder 2)
    - 1963-1964 (Box 1, Folder 3)
    - 1964-1965 (Box 1, Folder 4)
    - 1965-1966 (Box 1, Folder 5)
    - 1966-1967 (Box 1, Folder 6)
    - 1967-1968 (Box 1, Folder 7)
    - 1968-1969 (Box 1, Folder 8)
    - 1969-1970 (Box 1, Folder 9)
    - 1970-1971 (Box 1, Folder 10)
    - 1971-1972 (Box 1, Folder 11)
    - 1972-1973 (Box 1, Folder 12)
    - 1973-1974 (Box 1, Folder 13)
    - 1974-1975 (Box 1, Folder 14)
    - 1975-1976 (Box 1, Folder 15)
    - 1976-1977 (Box 1, Folder 16)
    - 1977-1978 (Box 1, Folder 17)
    - 1978-1979 (Box 1, Folder 18)
    - 1979-1980 (Box 1, Folder 19)
    - 1980-1981 (Box 1, Folder 20)
    - 1981-1982 (Box 1, Folder 21)
    - 1982-1983 (Box 1, Folder 22)
    - 1983-1984 (Box 1, Folder 23)
    - 1984-1985 (Box 1, Folder 24)
    - 1985-1986 (Box 1, Folder 25)
    - 1986-1987 (Box 1, Folder 26)
    - 1987-1988 (Box 1, Folder 27)
    - 1988-1989 (Box 1, Folder 28)
    - 1989-1990 (Box 1, Folder 29)
    - 1990-1991 (Box 1, Folder 30)
    - 1991-1992 (Box 1, Folder 31-31a)
    - 1993-1994 (Box 1, Folder 32-32a)
    - 1994-1995 (Box 1, Folder 33-33c)
    - 1995-1996 (Box 1, Folder 34-34a)
    - Original Annual report, 1996-1997 (Box 1, Folder 35)
    - Conflict of interest, Undated (Box 1, Folder 36)
  - Composite Teaching Evaluations
  - Course Evaluations - Faculty
    - Not used (Box 6, Folder 427)
    - Not used (Box 6, Folder 430)
    - Not received (Box 7, Folder 483)
    - Not used (Box 7, Folder 501)
    - 2002 Fall evaluations list (Box 8, Folder 540)
    - A, 2002 Fall (Box 8, Folder 541)
    - B, 2002 Fall (Box 8, Folder 542)
    - C-F, 2002 Fall (Box 8, Folder 543)
    - G, 2002 Fall (Box 8, Folder 544)
    - H-J, 2002 Fall (Box 8, Folder 545)
    - K, 2002 Fall (Box 8, Folder 545a)
    - L, 2002 Fall (Box 8, Folder 546)
    - M, 2002 Fall (Box 8, Folder 547)
    - N-R, 2002 Fall (Box 8, Folder 548)
    - S, 2002 Fall (Box 8, Folder 549)
    - T, 2002 Fall (Box 8, Folder 550)
    - W-Z, 2002 Fall (Box 8, Folder 551)
    - A-C, 2003 Spring (Box 8, Folder 555)
    - E-F, 2003 Spring (Box 8, Folder 556)
    - G, 2003 Spring (Box 8, Folder 557)
    - H, 2003 Spring (Box 8, Folder 558)
    - J-L, 2003 Spring (Box 8, Folder 559)
    - M-N, 2003 Spring (Box 8, Folder 560)
    - P-R, 2003 Spring (Box 8, Folder 561)
    - S, 2003 Spring (Box 8, Folder 562)
    - T-Z, 2003 Spring (Box 8, Folder 563)
  - Course Evaluations - Teaching Assistants
  - Course and Section Evaluations-Faculty
  - Course and Section Evaluations-Teaching Assistants
  - Personnel Files
  - Promotion Files
- Course evaluations, 2005-2010; Accession 2014-A-034
  Restricted until January 1, 2045.
  - Full Professor student course evaluations A-F, 2005 Fall (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Full Professor student course evaluations G-J, 2005 Fall (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Full Professor student course evaluations K-M, 2005 Fall (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Full Professor student course evaluations P-Z, 2005 Fall (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Associate Professor student course evaluations, 2005 Fall (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Assistant Professor student course evaluations, 2005 Fall (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Lecturer student course evaluations, 2005 Fall (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Visiting Professor student course evaluations, 2005 Fall (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Full Professor student course evaluations A-H, 2006 Fall (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Full Projessor student course evaluations I-Z, 2006 Fall (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Associate Professor student course evaluations A-Z, 2006 Fall (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Assistant Professor student course evaluations A-Z, 2006 Fall (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Lecturer student course evaluations A-Z, 2006 Fall (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Visiting Professor student course evaluations A-Z, 2006 Fall (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Post Doc student course evaluations A-Z, 2006 Fall (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - Full Professor student course evaluations A-G, 2006 Spr (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - Full Professor student course evaluations H-K, 2006 Spr (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - Full Professor student course evaluations M-P, 2006 Spr (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - Full Professor student course evaluations S-W, 2006 Spr (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - Associate Professor student course evaluations, 2006 Spr (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - Assistant Professor student course evaluations A-G, 2006 Spr (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - Assistant Professor student course evaluations L-Y, 2006 Spr (Box 1, Folder 22)
  - Lecturer student course evaluations, 2006 Spr (Box 1, Folder 23)
  - Miscellaneous evaluations, 2006 Spr (Box 1, Folder 24)
  - Visiting Professor student course evaluations, 2006 Spr (Box 1, Folder 25)
  - Post Doc student course evaluations, 2006 Spr (Box 1, Folder 26)
  - Full Professor student course evaluations A-L, 2007 Fall (Box 1, Folder 27)
  - Full Professor student course evaluations M-Z, 2007 Fall (Box 1, Folder 28)
  - Associate Professor student course evaluations A-Z, 2007 Fall (Box 1, Folder 29)
  - Assistant Professor student course evaluations A-Z, 2007 Fall (Box 1, Folder 30)
  - Lecturer student course evaluations A-Z, 2007 Fall (Box 1, Folder 31)
  - Visting Senior Lecturers student course evaluations, 2007 Fall (Box 1, Folder 32)
  - Lecturer Convertible student course evaluations, 2007 Fall (Box 1, Folder 33)
  - Post Doc student course evaluations A-Z, 2007 Fall (Box 1, Folder 34)
  - Full Professor student course evaluations A-H, 2007 Spr (Box 1, Folder 35)
  - Full Professor student course evaluations I-Z, 2007 Spr (Box 1, Folder 36)
  - Associate Professor student course evaluations A-Z, 2007 Spr (Box 1, Folder 37)
  - Assistant Professor student course evaluations A-Z, 2007 Spr (Box 2, Folder 38)
  - Lecturer student course evaluations A-Z, 2007 Spr (Box 2, Folder 39)
  - Visiting Professor student course evaluations, 2007 Spr (Box 2, Folder 40)
  - Full Professor student course evaluations A-H, 2008 Fall (Box 2, Folder 41)
  - Full Professor student course evaluations J-Z, 2008 Fall (Box 2, Folder 42)
  - Associate Professor student course evaluations, 2008 Fall (Box 2, Folder 43)
  - Assistant Professor student course evaluations, 2008 Fall (Box 2, Folder 44)
  - Lecturer student course evaluations, 2008 Fall (Box 2, Folder 45)
  - Full Professor student course evaluations, 2008 Spr (Box 2, Folder 46)
  - Associate Professor student course evaluations, 2008 Spr (Box 2, Folder 47)
  - Lecturer student course evaluations, 2008 Spr (Box 2, Folder 48)
  - Assistant Professor student course evaluations, 2008 Spr (Box 2, Folder 49)
  - Summer session evaluations 2008, 2008 Sum (Box 2, Folder 50)
  - Summer session evaluations 2009 & 2010, 2009 Sum-2010 Sum (Box 2, Folder 51)
  - Summer session evaluations 2010-non-tenured, 2010 Sum (Box 2, Folder 52)
  - Summer session evaluations 2010 tenured, 2010 Sum (Box 2, Folder 53)
  - Colonial History, 1984 (Box 12, Folder 25)
  - American History, 1967-1968 (Box 27, Folder 23)
  - Courses taught, committee assignments, essays and dissertations supervised, 1978-1979 (Box 36, Folder 30)